ED: Previously on Gotham...
Who were those people
you were speaking with?
You keep your nose
out of my business.
Come now, Butch. Play nice.
If a person comes into contact
with my blood, it changes them.
My brother, if he gets in
your mind, you're doomed.
Good-bye, Mr. Gordon.
- Ivy's missing.
- She'll turn up somewhere.
This time she fell.
It was a long way
down into water.
BRUCE: Then maybe she survived.
- MAN: What's your name?
- My name is Ivy.
Barnes asked me to put you
on a 48-hour suicide watch.
I've already signed off on it.
BUTCH: He just
cost you the election.
Give me one reason why I shouldn't
let Butch kill you where you stand.
There's that.
REPORTER: Oswald Cobblepot
has won the mayor's office by...
I believe in you, Oswald.
You never believed I could
win this election on my own.
Maybe you're not
cut out for this after all.
What?
Jervis. Let her go now.
No! I'll never go with you!
No!
(SCREAMING)
JERVIS: You killed her!
I would like to introduce
you to my chief of staff,
Mr. Edward Nygma!
(CROWD CHEERING)
MAN: (OVER PA) Welcome
your new mayor of Gotham,
Mayor Oswald Cobblepot.
Building Gotham safe again.
Welcome your new mayor of
Gotham, Mayor Oswald Cobblepot.
Building Gotham safe again.
(INAUDIBLE)
(CHEERING CONTINUES)
MAN: You're an angel.
Oh, thank you so
much. Thank you.
(CAMERAS CLICKING)
(CROWD WHOOPING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
Thank you.
COBBLEPOT: There's something
I've been wanting to ask you.
Am I a good boy?
Have I made you proud?
I hope I'm not interrupting.
Ah! Ed, you never met my mother.
Wasn't she beautiful?
A fine figure of a woman.
She was my whole world.
The only one that was
always there for me.
Well, I believe
the answer is yes.
She would be proud.
- Do you really think so?
- Oswald,
look at everything
you've achieved.
The people love you.
Gangs fear you.
And tomorrow night, the crème of
Gotham will be gathering to celebrate,
you.
What more could someone ask for?
Someone to share it with.
My mother was the
daughter of immigrants.
A humble cook.
We did not have much,
but when she was by my
side, I felt loved. Protected.
As promised, I have rid
Gotham of its villainous monsters.
With my mother as my witness, I
vow to you from this day forward,
every man, woman, and child
in our great city will be safe!
(CROWD CHEERING)
- (GUNSHOTS)
- (ALL SCREAMING)
RED HOOD: Spread out!
No one is safe.
Not from us. Drop it.
Put it down!
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(GASPING)
You will pay for this! Dearly!
RED HOOD: Now, now,
Mr. Mayor. Don't go losing your head.
(EXPLODES)
Have a nice day!
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
I can't come over tonight.
Okay.
I mean, that'd be three nights in a
row. That'd almost make it a thing.
Yeah. The neighbors might talk.
Exactly. And I have a dinner.
It's not a date.
None of my business.
Uh-huh.
So, whatever
happened with Tetch?
I told you.
He broke his sister
out of the GCPD.
Bullock and I chased him
down. She died. He escaped.
'Cause I heard a rumor there's
something strange about her blood.
Do you like this?
I think I've made
that pretty clear.
- Then why are you pressing?
- Because I want to know.
And are you asking as a
reporter, or as yourself?
- Is there a difference?
- There should be.
When you were a cop, did you stop
being one when you came home?
Maybe that was my problem.
Hmm.
The guy I'm having dinner
with is a hematologist
in charge of analyzing
Alice Tetch's blood.
I'm free after 10:00,
if you wanna call.
- Thanks for the coffee.
- (DOOR OPENS)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
We found the truck.
(GRUNTS)
BULLOCK: They
ditched it in The Narrows.
We've got forensics going over it,
and teams doing a 10-block sweep.
We already found this.
The Red Hood Gang?
I thought those
idiots were dead.
My guess is they're
copying the look.
The original Red Hood
Gang were bank robbers.
Whoever they are, they
got a beef with Penguin.
Expand the search to 15 blocks.
Everything goes through you.
ED: You mean through me.
Wow!
(LAUGHS)
It is good to be back.
I have missed all
of you. (CHUCKLES)
Harvey, still a stranger to a
haircut and a shave, I see.
What are you doing here, Nygma?
As Mayor Cobblepot's
chief of staff,
I'm gonna be your liaison on
the Red Hood investigation.
I wanna see all reports.
And I'm going to need
access to your forensic lab.
You think I'm gonna just let
you waltz into my precinct?
You're a cop killer who
should be in the loony bin.
- I'll be damned...
- You'll be fired.
The Mayor can't fire me.
No, but he can appoint a
police commissioner who will.
So, you will carry out the
Mayor's orders, without question,
or the GCPD has a new
captain. How does that sound?
Every dog has his day, Nygma.
Enjoy yours.
And where is our lord mayor?
Hiding under his desk?
He's meeting with constituents.
(COBBLEPOT SNIFFLES)
"Anything for you,
my little Cobblepot.
"You can count on me."
(SNIFFLES)
Those were the words my
mother used to whisper to me
every night
before I fell asleep.
She was a saint.
Yes, a saint whose only
desire was to love me.
And what was her thanks?
Not only did she take
a knife in the back,
but even in her death, her
memory is being desecrated.
Seriously? This is
the reason we're here?
A little glue. Some paint.
Momma will be good as new, huh?
- (LAUGHS)
- (GROANS)
No! That is not the
reason you are here.
The Red Hoods have
challenged my authority.
They will be made an example of.
Tonight, I am celebrating
my historic victory...
At The Sirens. It's gonna be
fabulous. None of you are invited.
I want them found, and their leader's head
brought to me on a spike before nightfall.
What're you waiting
for? Find them!
RED HOOD: All right.
Five card draw, gentlemen.
Someone didn't ante up.
Come on, you cheap bastards.
(SIGHS)
How long are we
supposed to wait?
Long as it takes the
boss man to get here.
You need a lookout.
(GUNS LOADING)
Ah, relax, fellas.
Hey, uh, you want us
to deal you in, boss?
We don't have time
for games, boys.
We got work to do.
- (KNOCKING ON DOOR)
- (DOOR OPENS)
Hello, Jim. Is it a bad
time? I should've called.
No.
Please, come in.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(SIGHS)
Right. Can I get you something
to drink? A glass of water?
I'm fine.
I heard you were back. I've
been meaning to come see you.
Everything okay?
Yes. Alfred and I are both well.
I hear you're a private
investigator now.
I'd like to hire you.
(SIGHS)
Bruce, if this is about
corruption at Wayne Enterprises...
It's not. I've put my investigation
into my father's company aside.
It's time I moved on.
Why the sudden change of heart?
It's far from sudden.
I've given it a great
deal of thought.
I can't live my life if
I keep looking back.
For what it's worth,
I think that's wise.
So, what can I do for you?
Ivy Pepper's gone missing.
I didn't realize
you two were close.
We're not. She's
a friend of Selina's.
And does Selina
know you're doing this?
No. I don't want to get her
hopes up if you don't find anything.
Well, we'll start with the GCPD.
See where we go from there.
And I think it's chivalrous,
you doing this for Selina.
How long have you
two been a thing?
Uh, no, no, no. Selina's
a friend. That's all.
- Mmm-hmm. Yeah.
- No. Really. She's just a friend.
Yeah. Yeah.
(ED WHISTLES)
Mr. Fox, just the man
I've been wanting to see.
Oh, joy. Mr. Nygma.
Heard you were stopping by.
I have questions.
Hopefully, you have answers.
Or what? You'll
poison me with gas?
(LAUGHS) That gas
was a sleeping agent.
And, to be fair, I was not
in the best place in my life.
(BLOWS)
To be fair, if you
ever threaten my life,
or the life of Bruce Wayne
again, I will find a way to end you.
Mr. Fox, we both know
you're not a man of violence.
No, I'm not.
If I was, I would have laced
some piece of lab equipment,
one which you were
sure to touch, with a toxin.
Ricin, maybe.
I'd use saxitoxin.
Harder to trace.
But I like your style.
You are insane.
Was insane. I
have a certificate.
So, the Red Hoods?
See for yourself.
Mmm?
(WHIRRING)
The gang's getaway vehicle
was abandoned in The Narrows.
As you'll notice,
its carpet fibers
has elements of dirt, oil,
and, oddly, potassium chloride.
A halide salt.
Fascinating.
So, nothing on Ivy Pepper.
But an odd report came
in a few weeks ago.
Okay, a construction
worker claimed
that a redhead knocked
him out, robbed him.
And she left this.
That's Ivy's sweater.
How do we find this man?
I already called.
All right, the guy's
down south on a job.
But he swore up and down that the
redhead who rolled him was in her 20s.
So? He's probably covering
for being with a young girl.
Doubtful he would come
forward in the first place.
Yeah. Most pervs don't wanna
call attention to themselves.
So, it wasn't Ivy.
It seems unlikely. But why
would she have Ivy's sweater?
- (FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
- Dr. Thompkins.
Bruce. It's good to see
you again. You got taller.
Like I said, right? The
kid's growing like a weed.
Nice to see you, too.
Uh, Jim, could I have a word?
I wanted you to hear it from me.
Um, my engagement announcement
is coming out in the Gazette tomorrow.
And it will feature
Mario's name.
I think that's customary.
His family name.
You mean Falcone.
You knew? You knew
and you didn't say anything?
Sure I did. I said
congratulations.
Don't be cute.
Lee. People talk.
Was I surprised? Sure.
But it's also none of my
business. Your life is your life.
And I meant what I said.
I'm very happy for you.
So, that's it?
That's it.
Okay. Um, well, I
just wanted to tell you.
(SIGHS)
Dr. Thompkins.
I had heard that you were back.
I'm so glad...
(GLASSES CLATTERING)
- That's for Kristen.
- You shouldn't have done that.
Or what? I'm supposed to be scared
of you because you work for Penguin?
My fiancé's father
is Carmine Falcone.
I so much as whisper to
him, and you disappear.
Tell the Mayor, whatever I
can do as ME, I'm happy to help.
It's bad enough we're
throwing Penguin's party.
- It's good for the club.
- Now we're his errand girls?
Sweetie, we find the
Red Hoods, he'll owe us.
We can ask for a favor.
Say, him not killing you?
Well, it would be nice not to
have to watch my ass all the time.
- (MAN WHIMPERING)
- (GASPS)
Well, well. Who do we have here?
Guy calls himself
The Ballistic Bomber.
My contact at The Merc saw him
buying smoke grenades last week.
Just like the ones the Red
Hoods used on Penguin.
Groovy. Reckon he'll talk?
Of course.
(WHIMPERS)
Maybe give him a moment.
Now, remember, kids, you tell
the press this is all Penguin's fault.
SISTER: Leave us, please!
- Good.
- Leave us in peace, please!
Okay, sir.
- Light it up.
- Have mercy.
PRIEST: Please. Don't. No!
Better run, Sister. Before
the Padre goes boom!
SISTER: No! Jesus! No!
Don't.
PRIEST: Wait, wait.
The grenade, it's slipping.
- (EXPLODES)
- (SCREAMS)
BUTCH: Seriously?
The priest? (CHUCKLES)
You should've seen it. Ka-boom!
But you told 'em what to say?
"This is all because of Penguin"?
Yeah, boss. But I don't get it.
You wanna take out
Penguin, let's take him out.
This Red Hood stuff is
fun, but it's a lot of work.
How about you just
do what I tell you.
Now, I got you these,
so you'll blend in
at the party tonight.
- Huh? Huh?
- Nice suit!
And that's when we kill him?
No!
No one kills Penguin!
TABITHA: You should.
'Cause he's gonna murder you!
(GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
Time to have a
heart to heart, Butch.
Alone.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
You don't have to buy lunch.
I know you're a billionaire.
But I can buy you a sandwich.
Do you miss it? Being a cop?
Sometimes. Yeah.
It gave a sense of mission.
True. There's more to
life than having a mission.
Look, I'll keep asking
around about Ivy. But, uh...
You want my
advice, talk to Selina.
Tell her how you feel.
Does that actually work?
Sometimes. It's definitely
better than being silent.
Before you know it,
the moment passes.
And are you taking
your own advice?
I'm afraid that ship has sailed.
I'm not talking about Dr. Thompkins.
I'm talking about the woman
- you're seeing now.
- Excuse me?
There was lipstick on a
coffee mug on your table.
You've become
quite the detective.
- (SIGHS)
- So, are you?
It's complicated.
So is Selina.
That I believe.
I just wish sometimes
I had a sign.
Unfortunately, life doesn't
usually work that way.
REPORTER: We're hours away from
Mayor Cobblepot's victory celebration.
But people are asking,
will the Red Hood Gang
put a damper on the festivities?
Sounds like Penguin's
having a bad day.
I'm supposed to go
to his party tonight.
Part of my re-engagement
with being a Wayne.
Hmm.
Well, give the Mayor my best.
(CHUCKLES)
Someone is testing me, Ed.
They're thinking, "He's mayor now.
He has to play by different rules."
No, they'll see, when I'm
roasting their entrails over a fire.
Perhaps I'm thinking
about this all wrong.
Perhaps, this is not about you at
all. What if this is about the statue?
Of course it's about me!
- Yes, you're probably right. Oh, dear.
- (GRUNTS)
- Wonderful.
- Oswald, take a breath.
(GRUNTING)
What are you doing?
It's an old trick I learned in the lab.
Most solvents have as their base...
I am the son of water, but if
water touches me, I die. What am I?
Again with the riddles?
Salt. Most people think
of it as a food additive.
But potassium salt is
found in detergents, soaps...
What is your point, Ed?
I know where the Red Hoods are.
BARBARA: I say we
give him to Penguin.
Knowing Penguin
will gut him like a fish?
Ladies. Come on. After
all we've been through...
It's his life for yours. Simple.
I don't get it. Why'd
you turn on him now?
I wasn't gonna hurt
Penguin, honest.
I was gonna take down
the Red Hoods myself.
Tonight, at the party.
All this so you
could play the hero?
Ever since Nygma
got out of Arkham,
Penguin treats
me like I'm nothing.
That pencil neck's
trying to push me out.
Let me ask you. We figured out
you're the man behind the Red Hoods.
How long do you think it'll
take Penguin and his lapdog?
It's your life, baby.
You make the call.
Let me see this through.
I get my place beside
Penguin back, I'll protect you.
Oh, you'll do more
than that. You'll owe me.
And one day, I'm gonna collect.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
- Gilzean.
- Butch, where are you?
The Red Hood Gang is at a
detergent factory in The Narrows.
We're on our way.
I gotta go.
Get your things. We're done.
I'm breaking up the band.
I'm serious. Go.
Get out of Dodge.
Yeah, well, not for nothing,
Butch, you promised us a payday.
We're not leaving
till we get it.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(CAR DOORS SLAMMING)
Well, guess it was gonna
happen sooner or later.
What?
Sorry, boys.
(ALL GRUNTING)
I did it, boss. I
got 'em for you.
(GASPING)
(CHUCKLES)
Peace and order have once
again been restored to Gotham.
The Red Hood Gang is no more.
My very own man, Butch Gilzean,
risked life and limb to
face down the bandits.
(REPORTERS CLAMORING)
Was your life ever
in danger, Butch?
I can honestly say
that if I'd had hesitated,
I'd have been a goner.
(COBBLEPOT CHUCKLES)
(CAMERAS CLICKING)
All right, people, listen
up. It's happy hour.
Finish up those reports,
and let's call it a day.
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
Hey, uh, Ed.
Even before you went
crazy, I never liked you.
Your zipper's down.
(SIGHS)
Listen, Butch did us all a favor.
Red Hoods go bye-bye. Case closed.
Look at the way the bodies fell.
It's as if they were just standing
there, waiting to be killed.
Butch comes all the way in the room.
But only one man pulled out a gun.
I guess they weren't threatened.
By a 300-pound gorilla?
Whose side are you
on anyway? Hmm?
No one's losing sleep over
a bunch of dead crooks.
Least of all me.
I said wrap it up!
What have we here...
Burning the midnight oil?
I was just finishing up.
I'm guessing you're
here to reprimand me.
Reprimand you? For what?
Punching Nygma in the jaw.
I just couldn't help myself.
First I'm hearing of it.
Well done, Doctor.
(CHUCKLES)
Actually, I'm here to ask
about, uh, Alice Tetch's blood.
If you've heard anything.
As it happens, I just received the
preliminary results back from the lab.
- Fascinating.
- What is?
They injected samples
into a group of rats.
After three days,
two of the rats
were showing marked
increases in strength and stamina.
Well, that doesn't sound so bad.
But the study ended after one
of the rats killed all the others.
I'm guessing that's not normal.
It chewed through a dozen
wire cages to get at them.
No.
Why would one of the rats
go psycho and not the others?
Perhaps the others hadn't had
a chance to show any symptoms.
Or they were immune.
Sometimes people live with a disease
for years without any adverse effects.
The lab is starting
a new study now.
Well, keep me informed.
Oh, and, uh,
don't stay too late.
I'm sure that fiancé of yours
would like to see you once in a while.
And was the captain of the GCPD
invited to our new mayor's victory party?
You know, I lost my invitation.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
I can feel it...
(MUSIC PLAYING)
My beautiful Oswald.
Heard you took down the
Red Hood Gang single-handed.
- So to speak.
- Very funny.
Don't forget. You owe me.
(SIGHS) I know.
(CAMERAS CLICKING)
How long do we have to stay?
As long as it takes for you to be
seen in the world, Master Bruce.
Being Bruce Wayne. And smiling.
So this is our life now?
Fake smiles and mingling.
I miss the old days.
So do I.
- It's so nice.
- Oh, excuse me.
Bruce, Mr. Pennyworth,
I'm so pleased you made it.
Yeah, well, you know, we're trying
to get out a bit more, Mr. Mayor.
Oh. Oswald, please.
We never got the chance to thank you
for saving our lives from the ex-Mayor.
- (CHUCKLES) That was nothing.
- ALFRED: Not at all.
I found it very fortuitous you turned
up when you did with that bazooka.
I just felt a bit sorry
for Stan, the gardener,
'cause he was picking up
bits of Galavan for weeks.
(CHUCKLES)
And now here you
are, the new mayor.
Sometimes life has
a way of working out.
Yes, that's true.
What is it, Master Bruce?
A sign.
Please excuse me.
ALFRED: All right, well,
I'll just go and wet my beak.
Congratulations
again, Mr. Mayor.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
- Hey!
- Hey yourself.
Funny, I never realized
how short you are.
Who the hell are you?
Not yet.
This is too fun.
Run along, little kitty.
Go steal some more wallets.
Hey.
So sweet.
There he is, the man of the hour.
I have a surprise for you, Butch.
Not in the mood.
What's in the box?
Open it.
(EXHALES)
Thanks, already got one.
Oh, of course you do.
And you certainly
wouldn't need this one,
as it's so similar to your
very own pocket square.
This is from the Red
Hood crime scene.
It turns out that your suit
and the Red Hood suits
were all made by the
same tailor, Mr. Fuji.
That's some coincidence.
I thought so myself, which
is why I called Mr. Fuji.
And he said that a large
man with a metal hand,
not many of those running
around, bought all six of the suits.
Which means, ta-da, you're
the architect of the Red Hood...
- (GRUNTS)
- I should snap your neck right now.
(CHOKING)
You haven't heard my offer.
(EXHALES)
We kill Penguin together.
(CHUCKLES)
What are you talking
about? You're his guy.
Oh, please. You
fell for that act?
Yes, he broke me out of
Arkham. Very appreciative.
But I was not cut out to be number two.
I've simply been waiting for my moment.
Which you have
graciously provided.
How would you like to
run Gotham with me?
(LAUGHS)
The two of us? Working together?
You have proven yourself far
more cunning than I imagined.
Now, I assume this little drama of
yours was meant to climax tonight.
So, put on the
hood, kill Penguin.
I'll help you escape.
Tomorrow, we divide up the city.
You'd really turn on him?
After all he did for you?
- Mr. P.
- In a heartbeat.
No.
Okay.
Then I guess it's time
for surprise number two.
You got to Zsasz?
I got to Zsasz.
And he got to Tabitha.
Penguin's history.
Question is, are you?
Can I see your invitation?
- (SIGHS) What are you doing here?
- I was invited.
Of course you were.
You recognize her?
Should I?
I don't know.
Hey. Are you, you?
I'm me.
Uh-huh. (CHUCKLES)
Well, I'm working, so...
Actually, there was
something I wanted to tell you.
Could we go
somewhere more private?
Fine. But make it quick.
Can't believe you'd
turn on Oswald, too.
Uh, hello. Pot-kettle-black.
No. It's not the
same thing. You...
Never mind.
I swear, your goons
hurt Tabitha, so help me...
Just do your job.
- (APPLAUSE)
- Huh.
Showtime.
Put one in the Mayor
before I put one in Tabitha.
Ladies, gentlemen.
Welcome to The Sirens.
Tonight we're here to celebrate
the honorable Mayor Cobblepot.
Our savior from the monsters,
and the captain of our fair city.
And now, the Mayor would
like to say a few words.
Ed, where've you been? I've
been looking for you all evening.
Oh, just tying up loose
ends. I just wanted to say
good luck.
(CHUCKLES) Okay. Thank you.
(CROWD CHEERING)
Tonight is a celebration,
not of my victory,
but of Gotham's.
This is a new day!
- (GUNSHOTS)
- (GASPS)
I wouldn't celebrate
yet, Mr. Mayor.
Red Hoods ain't finished yet.
- (GASPS) Ed! What are you doing?
- Wait!
Sorry, boss.
Butch!
- (GRUNTS)
- (CROWD EXCLAIMING)
(GASPS)
- Huh?
- Oops. (LAUGHS)
- (GUNSHOTS)
- (CROWD EXCLAIMING)
(GROANING)
The Mayor, our mayor,
vowed that all of the Red
Hoods would be destroyed.
And now we have
the real leader caught.
Red-handed.
(GROANING)
You really thought I'd
give you real bullets?
You are an idiot.
(CROWD EXCLAIMING)
I will kill you for this!
Sounds like we're
missing all the fun.
Got plenty of fun left for you.
You know, if you're gonna take
a girl hostage in her own place,
you might wanna search it first.
(GRUNTS)
After all that
I've done for you!
I gave you a job!
I gave you everything!
I used to be somebody in this town,
and then you and that sniveling little...
- (GRUNTS)
- (LAUGHS)
Shut up!
(GASPING)
I am shocked, and grieved,
that one of my dearest
friends has betrayed me.
But let it be known
that Oswald Cobblepot
will prosecute anyone
who threatens Gotham.
Hear, hear.
- Yeah!
- (CROWD CHEERING)
- Upsy-daisy.
- (GROANING)
- (GASPS)
- Oh, my God!
(LAUGHS)
Showtime.
(GUN CLATTERS)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
Oswald, move!
(GRUNTING)
I am gonna enjoy this!
(GASPING)
Best party ever.
(BOTTLE SHATTERS)
- Wait, not now.
- COBBLEPOT: Ed!
(GRUNTS)
Ed! Ed!
Ed!
(COUGHING)
So, what's up?
I hired Jim Gordon
to help me locate Ivy.
And?
There was a redhead that had
her sweater. But it wasn't Ivy.
Saying it out loud, I realize it
doesn't sound that impressive.
No. It doesn't.
That's really why you
brought me up here?
(SCOFFS)
You are the real Bruce,
'cause nobody else
would be this boring.
Great work, Detective.
That's not all.
We've been friends
a long time, Selina.
And ever since you've known me,
I have been dedicated to one thing.
But that's done.
I don't know what's
next. But I know...
Would you please just
say what you mean?
I like you.
As more than a friend.
It would be nice if you
said something back.
How many girls have you dated?
- What do you mean?
- (CHUCKLES)
It's not a trick question. How
many girls have you dated?
- None.
- None. Hmm.
Have you ever thought
that maybe you only like me
because I'm, literally,
the only girl you know?
That's not true. I feel something. And
I know you do, too. We're the same.
In what universe
are we the same?
- The money doesn't matter!
- Try not having it.
It matters.
There's something between us.
I know there is.
You have to see that.
Rule one,
don't ever tell me
what I have to do.
So, you do have feelings for me?
I'm confused.
Good.
Come on, just tell me.
I got all dressed up,
I even put on lipstick.
I could lose my job.
What are you offering?
Fine. Then I'll say something.
If I'm right, you just nod.
You ran tests on
Alice Tetch's blood?
You found something
in her blood.
A virus or infection
or something.
Do I have to go
over the rules again?
Let's have new rules, sweetie.
I'll tell you what we're doing
with Alice Tetch's blood,
and in return you...
Okay.
Excuse me, what are you doing?
(SIGHS)
Two whiskeys and a
pineapple juice for this guy.
- MAN: What's going on?
- To go.
What's going on?
I think you were just leaving.
Forget this.
Trust me, I'm gonna try.
(SIGHS)
What are you doing here?
Just walking by.
Saw you through the
window, took it as a sign.
Like hell.
You tracked me here.
And for the record, I could've
gotten what I wanted from that creep
without compromising my honor.
I know.
But you don't have to.
I'll tell you what
you wanna know.
I thought you wanted to keep the
woman and the reporter separate.
- Is that an option?
- No.
Well, then.
You are gonna have to
buy me dinner though.
What's good here?
(COUGHING)
It's ginger tea with honey.
It's my mother's
remedy for a sore throat.
You sure you don't
need a doctor?
No. I'm fine.
(COUGHS)
I still don't understand why you
didn't tell me what you were doing.
Your shock, when seeing
Butch, had to be genuine.
The people had to believe it.
And they did. And once
again, you're the city's hero.
(CHUCKLES)
You were almost killed.
And you saved me. Again.
(COUGHS)
I hope you know, Oswald,
I would do anything for you.
You can always count on me.
Thank you.
Need a hand, kitten?
I got it.
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
(GUN LOADING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
Hold on, Butch.
Sir, the ambulance carrying
Butch Gilzean was just hijacked.
Damn it! Put out a
BOLO. I'll call the Mayor.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Yes.
WOMAN: (STAMMERS)
Mister, please.
(JERVIS SHUSHING)
My dear, sweet sister.
Just look at what he did to you.
He took you from me!
We belonged together.
And he killed you.
But, mister, I'm not dead.
If only that were true.
(GASPING)
Those who hurt you
will feel my pain,
when my sweet and
terrible vengeance
upon them rains.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
English -SDH